Guide to the Stanford University, School of Engineering, Dean's Office, Records SC0165
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- General Correspondence, Series 1
  - Vibration Research, 1926-1929 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    Correspondence, memoranda, and reports by Theodore Hoover, Bailey Wil1is, E.P. Lesley, Charles Moser, and James Macelwane (Saint Louis University) on earthquake study and its relation to various phases of engineering and architectural study. Also correspondence about research work done using specially construted shaking tables; and on earthquake activated valves designed to shut off gas and electricity in the event of a quake.
  - Vibration Research, 1930-1937 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Vibration Research: Reports, 1929-1930 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    Reports on tentative program of vibration research; motion of soil subjected to a ground vibration; analytical solution of the dynamics of the impact vibrating table, and experimental study of the dynamic behavior of wood nodels.
  - V - general correspondence, 1935-1945 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - V - general correspondence, 1946-1955 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Wade, Jeptha, 1940-1941 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    Designing Engineer for California Water Service Company. Correspondence with Dean Morris requesting his recommendations for filling engineering vacancies at the mompany.
  - Warren, Earl, 1942-1945 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    Governor of California. Correspondence from Dean Morris to Warren urging the governor's retention of Henry Dewell on State Board of Registration for Civil Engineers; recommending appointment of A.I. Stewart as Director of Department of Professional and Vocational Standards; copies of correspondence between President Tresidder and Warren about Stanford's representation at a state-widewater conference.
  - War Department, 1937-1944 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    Recommendations for students wishing appointments in various branches of the arned forces; information on Army Reserve Engineering Commissions; War Department requests for technical manpower.
  - Ward, Eugene, 1932-1945 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    Lecturer in Architectural Engineering. Correspondence about the terms of his appointment; recommendations for pre-architectural curriculum at Stanford; class scheduling; engineering classroom renovations.
  - Warm, Otto, 1937-1944 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    Laboratory Mechanic for Civil Engineering. Correspondence about his application for position at Stanford; letters ofrecommendation; reports of accidents involving Warm; salary matters.
  - Washington, University of, 1931-1941 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    Folder contains correspondence with two different institutions: the University of lVashington (Seattle), and Washington University (Saint Louis). Correspondence between Dean Hoover, Dean Morris and Engineering Deans and faculty members at these universities on topics related to engineering education.
  - Wells, James Bertram, 1928-1946 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    Professor of Structural Engineering in the Mechanical Engineering Department. Wells' application materials: resume, qualifications, bibliography, recommendations; appointment to the faculty'; proposed structural engineering curriculum; reports on material strength testing. Correspondence about C. H. Snyder's gift of architectural drawings and computations to Engineering School; miscellaneous technical inquiries on structural engineering problems.
  - Westinghouse Company, 1926-1939 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    Correspondence between Westinghouse Company executives and Engineering School about Westinghouse Scholarships; employment opportunites; engineering school curriculum and its relation to conmercial employment; Westinghouse publications; Company continuing education programs.
  - White, Ross, 1935-1941 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Construction Superintendent of the T.V.A.; later engineer with private firm; friend of Dean Morris. Correspondence with Morris on employment opportunities rvith the T.V.A.; Morris' recomnendations about particular candidates; dam construction.
  - Whitman, Ray, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Correspondence with Dean Morris on Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering; patents; Whitman Ranch.
  - Wickersham, L. B., 1929-1930 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Correspondence with Dean Hoover about his son's application to Stanford; death of a common friend, Arthur Sandstrom.
  - Wiedmann, Milton, 1942-1945 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Professor of Mechanical Engineering. Memoranda about his application; appointment; teaching load; resignation from Stanford.
  - Williams, Harry, 1931-1944 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Professor of Civil Engineering. Resume, biographical and bibliographical materials connected with application for teaching position at Stanford and the University of Missouri; correspondence about materials testing at Stanford; attendence at professional conferences; course work.
  - Willis, Bailey, 1924-1938 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Professor of Geology. Correspondence with Dean Hoover on concrete structure; seismographs; geological reports on the site of proposed Lafayette Reservoir and mechanical faulting of the San Francisco Peninsula; earthquake engineering research; hydroelectric development in Formosa; seismic conditions affecting the Golden Gate Bridge.
  - Wing, Charles B., 1915, 1925-1936 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Executive Head of Civil Engineering Department. Memoranda with Dean's Office on various aspects of department business; committee memberships; equipment; curriculum. "Report on the failure of the North Tower of the South San Francisco Station of the Federal Telegraph Company," by C.B. Wing.
  - Wolman, Abel, 1937-1944 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Chief Engineer, State of Maryland Department of Health. Friend of Dean Morris. Correspondence with Morris on professional activities; flood control; national water legislation.
  - Woods, Baldwin, 1933-1935, 1938-1943 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Chairman of the Mechanical Engineering Department at the University of California, Berkeley; mernber of the National Resources Planning Board. Correspondence with Dean Morris about engineering education at Stanford and Berkeley; water resources; development of the Pacific Southwest.
  - Women in Engineering, 1943-1945 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Lists of women engineering students for these academic years.
  - W - general correspondnece, 1923-1938 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - W - general correspondnece, 1939-1942 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - W - general correspondnece, 1943-1945 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - W - general correspondnece, 1946-1955 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Young, Donovan, 1928-1946 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    Graduate student, later Professor of Civil Engineering. Correspondence related to application for fellowship and teaching position at Stanford; biographical and bibliographic information; appointment; proposed Institute of Engineering Mechanics.
  - Young, W.W., 1929-1945 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    Teaching specialist in Foundry Practice. Correspondence and biographical material related to application for position; appointment and reappointment notices.
  - X, Y, Z - general correspondence, 1919, 1925-1939 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - X, Y, Z - general correspondence, 1940-1944 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - X, Y, Z - general correspondence, 1946-1955 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Appointments, Series 2
  - Aeronautical Engineering: Besseling, Johannes, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Aeronautical Engineering: Nickel, Lyman Charles, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Aeronautical Engineering: miscellaneous, 1957-1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Bourke, Brown, Bryson, Chilver, Clarke, DeBra, Eversman, Fleming, Frederick, Gui1liot, Guiraud, Hayashi, Hemp, Heaslet, Humbard, Hsaio, Kyser, McIntosh, Matzkevitch, Nadir, Pao, Pringle, Rosen, Stuart, Uemura, Vali, DeVeubeke, Vogel, Wiesner, Young.
  - Chemical Engineering: Miscellaneous, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Adamson, Baerg, Bizzell, Cromwell, Fong. Micheli, Muzzy, Paalman, Schoofs, Stonehart.
  - Civil Engineering: Baldwin, Leonard B., 1956-1958 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ciyil Engineering: Matheu, Robert Richard, 1948-1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Civil Engineering: Wells, James B., 1948-1954 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Civil Engineering: miscellaneous, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Abramson, Adams, Anderson, Andrews, Bennett, Biegel, Blenby, Browning, Brummett, Bunnell, Burgess, Burnham, Burns, Carstensen, Chase, Dennis, Dunlap, Edwards, Evaldson, Fick, Granick, Gordon, Halderman, Hamilton, Harris, Hash, Hooley, Hubbard, Hunt, Irani, Jackson, Johnson, Johnston, King, Kline, Knudson, Lamore, Lev, Lewis, Liljenwall, Logan.
  - Civil Engineering: miscellaneous, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Ma, McLain, Maneatis, Marriott, Marthandam, Matheu, Morshead, Moser, Murray, Napper, Neuerburg, Petersen, Phelps, Phillips, Pott, Price, Read, Rehmus, Roberts, Sale, Sawyer, Sutherland, Szego, Todd, VanSickel, Walker, Warm, Wells, Zaid.
  - Civil Engineering: miscellaneous, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Alramani, Aspinwall, Brenkert, Crane, Dunn, Fritschle, Kaechele, Kendall, Kennedy, LaFlamme, Leighton, Lieberman, Loewenthal, MacNeur, Matheu, Paul, Phelps, Richey, Ring.
  - Civil Engineering: miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Baldwin, Benike, Bestwick, Binkley, Brenker, Curley, Fair, Fyfe, Hannaford, Holton, Hsai, Kenda1l, Kennedy, LaFlamme, Lehmann, Nevin, Noah, Nomikos, Paul, Richey, Siegfried, Skyles, Walter, Wood, Zeiler.
  - Civil Engineering: miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Baldwin, Binkley, Cleverly, Duncan, Edson, Elsessner, Fyfe, Hannaford, Heebink, Hiramatsu, Jones, Kendall, Kennedy, Kleerup, LaFlamme, Leckie, Lin, Maranda, Mathias, Meigs, Oakford, Osborn, Perry,Richards, Robertson, Sah, Smith, Williams, Wood.
  - Civil Engineering: miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Colb, Dunn, Fyfe, Garrard, Geary, Hershberger, Hill, Hong, Julien, Kendall, Kennedy, Kornelsen, Leckie, Meigs, Morgali, Noren, Perry, Skyles, Smith, Steele, Stone, Walter, Wood.
  - Civil Engineering: miscellaneous, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Alltucker, Blume, Clark, Cobb, Cone, Crawford, Dahlke, Deltilest, Dunn, Field, Florence, Griffin, Hi11, Kendall, Kennedy, Leckie, Liggett, Lindberg, Lorh, Luck, Matheu, Morel-Seytoux, Morgali, Morris, Raffin, Richards, Robertson, Schley, Steele, Street, Walter, Wilsea
  - Civil Engineering: miscellaneous, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Alltucker, Binkley, Blume, Blythe, Chalmers, Cone, Dahlke, DeWiest, Duncan, Field, Hsu, Hutchinson, Irmay, Kelly, Kendall, Kennedy, King, Lohr, Matheu, Medearis, Morel-Seytoux, Morgali, Morris, Munro, Parson, Raffin, Richardson, Riplog, Robertson, Rowland, Smith, Teicholz, Williams, Wilson, Wolf
  - Civil Engineering: miscellaneous, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Adamson, Bartle, Carter, Dahlke, Dyckman, Feng, Field, Gordon, Green, FIall, Hassan, Holmes, Hua, Julien, Kendall, Kirkwood, Kneese, Lenau, Mah, Morris, Pattison, Paxson, Peugh, Riplog, Rowland, Royce, Shah, Teicholz, Thorpe, Toossi, Vyas, Wary, Watters, Williams, Winfrey, Wolf
  - Electrical Engineering: Blanchard, Henry P, 1942-1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Electrical Engineering: Bourquin, Burnice, 1937-1954 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Electrical Engineering: Hare, Milton Dixon (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Electrical Engineering: Scarlett, Robert N., 1958-1961 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Electrical Engineering: Wade, Glen, 1957-1960 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Electrical Engineering: miscellaneous, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Bahrs, Brunetti, Buss, Clark, Cohn, Cone, Crumly, Duffy, Dunn, Edson, Elliott, Evans, Gehrels, Granger, Hammond, Harris, Harroun, Hayes, Herrero, Hewlett, Heyning, Hobson, Jarnison, Johnson, Jo11yman, Kaisel, Kastner, Lee, Levin, Lewis, Loh, McWhorter, Marggraf, Oliver, Packard, Panholzer, Peterson, Rowton, Sargent, Schulz, Smith, Stearns, Stewart, Susskind, Taylor, Thomas, Tweedon, VanValkenburg, Wightman, Winnkleman, Yabroff, Yeh.
  - Electrical Engineering: miscellaneous, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Abramson, Birdsall, Boxnall, Bracewell, Buss, Chen, Cone, deBroekart, Duffy, Dunn, Edson, Elliott, Embry, Franks, Gehrels, Goldstein, Granger, Hammond, Harris, Harroun, Hewlett, Heyning, Hiramatsu, Hobson, Johnson, Jollyman, Kaisel, Kohl, Kronmiller, Kurzweil, Lee, Lim, Linguetti, Loh, McLean, McWhorter, Marggraf, Mathias, Melkonian, Misra, Moreno, Myers, Noe, Oliver, Packard, Paddock, Panholzer, Pantell, Peterson, Rambo, Sah, Salmon, Sargent, Sharp, Smaus, Smith, Solner, Spilker, Storke, Tompkins, Tweeden, Walker, Waterman, Whitby, Williams, Yhap
  - Electrical Engineering: miscellaneous, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Abramson, Anderson, Bennett, Berg, Bodine, Buneman, Buss, Cone, Crandall, DeBroekart, Dunn, Edson, Elliott, Eshelman, Fein, Kralick, Franks, Grace, Granger, Gronemann, Harris, Harroun, Hervlett, Ho, Hockett, Holland, Ishikawa, Johnson, Kerwin, Kincheloe, Kohl, Kronmiller, Kurzrveil, Lang, Lee, Levin, MacArthur, McWhorter, Maley, Moreno, Nilsson, Noe, Nogle, Oliver, O'Neill, Panholzer, Pantell, Rambo, Regenos, Reyna, Salmon, Sargent, Sharp, Shockley, Shumate, Smith, Solnar, Spilker, Turner, Wade, Waterman, Webster, Weiss, Yhap
  - Electrical Engineering: miscellaneous, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Abramson, Aitchison, Alvarez, Ames, Anderson, Bahr, Bahrs, Baron, Bennett, Berg, Boxnal1, Brandstatter, Bunernan, Burco, Buss, Butcher, Cage, Cannon, Carlin, Carlson, Casey, Chang, Cohn, Cone, Cumming, deBroekert, Dow, Dunn, Edson, Elliott, Ellman, Eshelman, Feinstein, Flammer, Foell, Fontana-Rabel, Franks, Gillmore, Glavitsch, Golde, Gould, Grace, Grigsby, Herold, Hewlett, Holland, Holmes, Isberg, Israelsen, Johnson, Kautz, Kerlin, Kincheloe, Kino, Kirstein, Kohl, Kurzweil, Lathi, Lauritzen, Lee, Levin, Ligomenides, Lindliolm, Loew, Lusignan, McDonald, Maley, Matthaei, Montgomery, Moore, Moreno, Mosher, Nelson, Noe, Norby, Oliver, Paddock, Pedersen, Perkins, Peschon, Petriceks, Phillips, Pratt, Scott, Shockley, Skahill, Smith, Soudack, Spangenberg, Stearns, Stewart, Strohbehn, Templeton, Thomassen, Thompson, Tobey, VanDuzer, VanLantschoot, VanSaun, Wade, Waterman, Weld, Yabroff, Yin, Zeheb
  - Electrical Engineering: miscellaneous, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Aalseth, Aufenkamp, Bahrs, Barry, Belser, Bennett, Bernard, Black, Braverman, Brechna, Brenner, Burrus, Carlson, Carswell, Chang, Chatters, Chen, Christie, Creason, DeBra, DeBroekert, Denno, DiDomenico, Ebenhoch, Elspas, Fontana, Fowler, Frye, Gary, Gillette, Grettenberg, Grigsby, Hunter, Hutchison, Hutter, Hyatt, Johnson, Kakinuma, Kempf, Kertvin, Kroitzsh, Landshoff, Leake, Linden, Lindsay, Logiadis, Louisell, Lovinfosse, Matthaei, Meyer, Michice, Morris, Mosher, Murphy, Nilsson, Norby, Padulo, Panholzer, Pease, Peschon, Pettit, Rosen, Ross, Rushforth, Saulich, Schoenberger, Schlomann, Schramm, Seeger, Shockley, Stoff, Thompson, Van Lantschoot, Wade, Ward, Weigle, Yngvesson, Young, Zajec
  - Industrial Engineering: Freeman, Jack, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Industrial Enginegring: Henderson, Clark, 1948-1953 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Industrial Engineering: Norton, Paul, 1952-1954 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Industrial Engineering: Smith, Barnard Elliott, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Industrial Engineering: miscellaneous, 1955-1960 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Adams, Bindschdler, Bowker, Brackenridge,Brown, Carvell, Fair, Frane, Gessford, Gomberg, Hillier, Jones, Kilbridge, Koenigsberg, LaFlamme, McKim, McLarney, Moore, Norton, Oakford, Richardson, Roy, Schweizer, Smith, Steele, Stone, Story, Swalm, Thompson, Vaughn, Waggoner, White
  - Industrial Engineering: miscellaneous, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Canada, Capron, Cowles, Fleischer, Giglio, Gomberg, Hall, Halsted, LaFlamme, Leavenworth, Longnecker, McLarney, Marshall, Matchett, Moore, Morrissey, Ostergren, Reul, Riggs, Robichek, Savesky, Saylor, Smith, Story
  - Materials Science: miscellaneous, 1960-1965 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Anderson, Ardeli, Barbee, Barrett, Burmeister, Bush, Clinard, daCamera, Dils, Donnelly, Fischer, Goetzel, Goldman, Grebe, Gulden, Hammad, Hinzer, Hren, Joseph, Kamer, Keith, Kendrick, Kinsman, Klein, Larsen-Badse, Lauritzen, Malinda, Massalski, Mash, Miller, Nattkemper, Nelson, Parks, Peirce, Prasad, Radjy, Reed, Robbins, Roust, Rudee, Saxton, Sheinker, Silva, Sklensky, Smallman, Stoebe, Thomas, Vlaschitz, Vohtz, Wilcox, Zebraski, Zupp
  - Mechanical Engineering: Ayre, Robert, 1946-1952 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Mechanical Engineering: Birnie, Hans, 1948-1958 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Mechanical Engineering: Brown, Wayne, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Mechanical Engineering: Daane, Robert A., 1958-1961 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Mechanical Engineering: Green, Boynton, 1926-1959 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Mechanical Engineering: Hugo, Merrill, 1935-1946 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Mechanical Engineering: Phillips, Aris, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Mechanical Engineering: Rowe, Albert, 1942-1960 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Mechanical Engineering: Salisbury, J. Kenneth, 1952-1956 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Mechanical Engineering: miscellaneous, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Adams, Allen, Armstrong, Barber, Barsotti, Belew, Belmont, Benson, Brahtz, Brannaman, Byington, Camp, Christopher, Clalson, Danforth, Dannenberg, Dygert, Evenson, Ford, Frederick, Gaslch, Hartnan, Honka, Huggins, Hughes, Inouye, Johnson, Keene, Lattin, Legg, Lewis, Locke, Longwell, McCandless, McFadden, Meyn, Miloglav, Myhre, O'Connor, Ono, Phipers, Proctor, Rensch, Roinestad, Sarson, Schweizer, Smith, Staros, Tange, Thomas, Tinling, Van Wye, Vincenti, Wellington, Woods
  - Mechanical Engineering: miscellaneous, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Baggs, Benson, Beroza, Birnie, Brown, Browing, Chamberlain, Chang, Coppage, Dane, Dannenberg, Diehl, Eding, Fralow, Ford, Garrard, Graham, Hancock, Huggins, Inouye, Jones, Laddon, Lee, Locke, Longwell, McCown, Martin, Merjeyevsky, Milog1av, Moser, Murcock, Murray, Nakamoto, Meou, Niteberg, Ono, Oppenheim, Peterson, Price, Proxtor, Reed, Reynolds, Sale, Saphra, Sarson, Spraggins, Steinbliss, Tom, Triplett, Waters, Whittemore, Wulff, Wyss, Zaid, Zeile
  - Mechanical Engineering: miscellaneous, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Adams, Baggs, Bissleri, Brain, Browning, Bunnell, Burgess, Carney, Clark, Dane, DeCamp, Denkers, Diehl, Gryer, Edward, Fietzer, Finberg, Garnick, Gilman, Glassner, Graham, Hancock, Hattersley, Johnson, Kaatteri, K1ine, Lee, Lloyd, Lo, Locke, McCown, McDonald, Macinko, Marchand, Marriott, Martin, Moser, Muffley, Murray, Nakamoto, Neou, Ono, Oppel, Paine, Phillips, Rao, Rice, Sarson, Seenel, Shimmon, Sonneman, Todd, Tom, Wyss, Youle, Zaid
  - Mechanical Engieering: miscellaneous, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    Baca, Behr, Chamberlain, Chapman, Chubbock, Coppage, Crumly, Dane, Dannenberg, DeAngelis, Flugge-lotz, Freeman, Gayling, Heaslet, Harris, Irwin, Johnson, Jones, Kaatteri, Kline, Lee, Lo, Lomax, Lorber, Lynch, Marchand, Minkoff, Murray, Neou, Oppel, Page, Potter, Rao, Scollay, Seemel, Sorenson, Spokely, Tom, Toney, Vincenti, Watts, Werlin, Wing, Wood
  - Mechanical Engineering: miscellaneous, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    Aisawa, Burger, Carson, Chamberlain, Chapman, Flugge- Lotz, Hancock, Heasl et, Johnson, Jones, Landis, Lomax, Lorber, Mekler, Nakamoto, Ono, Sarson, Scollay, Simpson, Spreiter, Tsuruda, VanDyke, Vincenti
  - Mechanical Engineering: miscellaneous, 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Begg, Bennett, Caryotikis, Chapman, Clark, Coppage, Edwards, Hancock, Heaslet, Howard, Jones, Landis, Lomax, McKin1ey, Pefley, Sarson, Spreiter, Stuart, Thomas, VanDyke, Vincenti, Young
  - Mechanical Engineering: miscellaneous, 1954-1957 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    Bahjat, Banham, Begg, Bennett, Bradley,Bulkeley, Chamberlain, Chapman, Cochran, Coddington, Costell, Dawson, Day, Drummond, Eustis, Hancock, Harper, Heaslet, Ikebe, Jones, Laitone, Lomax, McDowelm, McKenzie, McKinley, Rogers, Rosen, Sarson, Schmitt, Schoenberger, Spreiter, Stuart, VanDyke, Vincenti, Wiesner, Wetherly
  - Mechanical Engineering: miscellaneous, 1958-1960 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    Adams, Barrington, Bradley, Broido, Bulkeley, Burgess, Bush, Chamberlain, Cima, Colah, Costello, Cranch, Davies, Duddeck, Goto, Harris, Hofmayer, Ikebe, Jordan, Keller, Kikukawa, Knights, Lowell, Luke, McCuen, McKenzie, McKim, McKinley, Matsumoto, Mitchell, Murray, Myers, Nicoll, O'Connor, Pickett, Renner, Rosen, Sarson, Schoenberger, Schulte, Sjostrand, Smith, Taylor, Test, Tipei, Tomsicek, Trager, Tutcotto, Vaughn, Vliet, Webster, Yoshida
  - Mechanical Engineering: miscellaneous, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    Admani, Barrington, Biggs, Bitch, Bohnstedt, Bradley, Cannon, Chamberlain, Clenent, Cobb, Emo Capodilesta, Etemad, Gardner, Gilleo, Gross, Hashmatrai, Heaton, Ikebe, Judah, Keller, Kendall, Leifer, NIcCuen, McKinley, Martin, Metzger, Moretti, Myers, O'Connor, Ragent, Rogers, Sagi, Sarson, Schraub, Schweitzer, Smith, Supple, Tibbetts, Tiederman, Tutcotte, Uzkan, Yoshida
- Budgets, Series 3
  - 1925-1926 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1932-1933 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1933-1934 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1934-1935 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1941-1942 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Summer Quarter 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Summer Quarter 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Summer Quarter 1949 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Summer Quarter 1950 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Summer Quarter 1951 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - 1952-1953 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Working materials and notes for 1952-1953 budget (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Working materials and notes for 1954-1955 budget (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Working materials and notes for 1955-1956 budget (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Working materials and notes for 1956-1957 budget (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Working materials for 1959-1960 budget (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Annual Reports to the President, Series 4
  - Reports, 1945-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Dean's Office, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Civil Engineering Department, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Electrical Engineering, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Mechanical Engnineering, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Mining Engineering, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Dean's 0ffice, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Electrical Engineering, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Dean's Office, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Civil Engineering, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Electrical Engineering, including drafts, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Dean's 0ffice, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Civil Engineering, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Electrical Engineering, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Dean's Office, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Civil Engineering, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Electrical Engineering, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Reports, 1950-1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Dean's Office, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Civil Engineering, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 2)